{
    "id": "wannabeyouth",
    "name": "wanna be youth",
    "yomi": "ワナビーユース",
    "text": [
        "散歩したり、宅録したりしています",
        "I just take a walk and recording at home."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Twitter",
            "href": "https://www.twitter.com/wannabe_youth/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Which do you prefer?",
            "jp": "選ぶならどっち？",
            "yes": "love someone",
            "left": "愛したい",
            "no": "being loved by someone",
            "right": "愛されたい"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Do you like human?",
            "jp": "人間は好き？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "嫌い"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "The eyes are the windows to the soul. agree?",
            "jp": "目は口ほどに物を言う？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "そう思う",
            "no": "No i don't think so",
            "right": "そう思わない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you want to be forgiven?",
            "jp": "許されたい？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Which do you like?",
            "jp": "浴びるなら？",
            "yes": "sun light",
            "left": "日光",
            "no": "moon light",
            "right": "月光"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Which do you rely on?",
            "jp": "どっちを頼りにする？",
            "yes": "knowledge",
            "left": "知識",
            "no": "experience",
            "right": "経験"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Do your footprints leave?",
            "jp": "あなたの足跡は？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "残る",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "残らない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Which would you like to be?",
            "jp": "なるとしたら",
            "yes": "a spherical object",
            "left": "球体",
            "no": "a cube",
            "right": "立方体"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Eventually",
            "jp": "ゆくゆくは？",
            "yes": "we will fly",
            "left": "空を飛ぶ",
            "no": "we will crawl on the ground",
            "right": "地を這う"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "The important thing should be",
            "jp": "大事なことは",
            "yes": "shared",
            "left": "共有する",
            "no": "kept a secret",
            "right": "一人で愛でる"
        }
    ]
}